

HAO NGO

FRONT-END

PERSONAL INFORMATION

DOB: 15 Jan 2000

Gender: Male

Phone: 0944334052

Email: ngotrieuhao@gmail.com Address: District 8, Ho Chi Minh

City

Github: github.com/ngotrieuhao

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/h%E1%BA%A3o-

ng%C3%B4-795998184/

Website:

https://ngotrieuhao.github.io/portfo

liohtmljs/

OBJECTIVE

Apply the knowledge learned in school and self-study about building a website to experience in a dynamic and professional environment. From there, develop professional skills, learn new programming knowledge to successfully complete the assigned work.

SKILLS

- Hard skill
 - HTML
 - CSS
 - Javascript

Soft skill

- Teamwork
- Self-Study
- Problem-Solving

EDUCATION

Major: Information Technology

WORKING EXPERIENCE

2021/11 - 2022/2

Nata Jsc Company

Role: Front-End Developer (Website & Mobile)
Responsibilities:

- Plan ideas and work together with team design
- Write website code with programming -

languages such as: HTML, CSS and Javascript

- Fix bugs that arise

2021/06 - 2021/12

E-commerce Website (Shoes Store)

Role: Front-End Developer

Responsibilities:

- Plan ideas and sketch out diagram
- Write website code with programming languages such as: HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Fix any website issues or bugs that arise
- Turn UI/UX designs into prototypes, create excellent interactions from designs

2021/01 - 2021/04

Student Management Website

Role: Front-End Developer Responsibilities:

- Write website code with programming languages such as HTML, CSS and Javascript
- Turn UI/UX designs into prototypes, create excellent interactions from designs